virtualtaboo.com 2017-02-19

# Privacy policy, VirtualTaboo

At [www.virtualtaboo.com](http://www.virtualtaboo.com/) your privacy is absolutely important to us. We are fully committed to protecting your personal information. For this reason we will not distribute, rent or sell your personal information or distribute information to third parties without user authorization, unless needed for using the service. We do not have any access to your credit card information. For your protection, user credit card details are handled exclusively by our credit card processors, and not by us.

According to the principles of the Processing of Personal Data (Protection of Individual Law 2001 (138(1)/2001)) all data voluntarily provided by users on this website will be stored in a file whose ownership corresponds to the named company; in this case CAMON TRADING LTD. The user/customer, has the right to exercise their rights of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition by addressing our Support team (support@virtualtaboo.com) or with a physical letter (adding a copy of your passport or personal identification) to the following address of our company:

Camon Trading LTD  
Arch Makariou III 135  
EMELLE BUILDING, 4th floor  
3021, Limassol, Cyprus 

CAMON TRADING LTD complies with current data protection legislation and specifically with the Cypriot "Processing of Personal Data (Protection of Individual Law 2001 (138(1)/2001)) as well as all other legislation governing the sector of activity in which they have discharged CAMON TRADING LTD.

The information requested by CAMON TRADING LTD via any of our web sites (especially www.virtualtaboo.com), such as a user’s e-mail address, name, surname, phone, etc... Has the objective of the proper functioning of the page and the corresponding user accounts. CAMON TRADING LTD may also use these e-mail addresses of its users to send information related to this website and possibly for advertising purposes too. We understand that the user understand, consents and expressly authorizes the forwarding of information and publicity from CAMON TRADING LTD to their respective email addresses.

Adhering with current regulations, CAMON TRADING LTD collects only the data strictly necessary to provide the services resulting from its activities and other facilities, services and activities assigned by law, such as statics purposes.

This data protection policy may change over time due to possible legislative changes, case law or changes in criteria made by the Spanish Agency for Data Protection and / or the competent authority at all times. Therefore CAMON TRADING LTD reserves the right to amend this legal notice to correlate with new legislation or jurisprudence which is in force at the precise moment you access to websites, as well as industry practices.

In the above scenario CAMON TRADING LTD will introduce prospective changes on their website before implementation.

The input of your data on our websites implies the acceptance of these terms of use and privacy policy, with the understanding that the user is informed of the conditions of use and privacy policy for them and is committed to full compliance while visiting in www.virtualtaboo.com.

This data protection policy may change over time due to possible legislative changes, case law or changes the criteria followed by the Cyprus Office of the Commissioner for Personal Data Protection and / or the competent authority at all times. That is why CAMON TRADING LTD reserves the right to amend this legal notice to adapt to new legislation or jurisprudence which are in force at the precise moment you access to websites, as well as industry practices.

**Cookies:** This site uses cookies to deliver its services. VirtualTaboo assumes you understand and agree this, if you keep using our site. Read more
